<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Tier0 Network</title>
    <link>https://t0.network/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Tier0 Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://t0.network/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>For Clients</title>
      <link>https://t0.network/about/1-clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://t0.network/about/1-clients/</guid>
      <description>Who are you? We are a small remote team currently based on São Paulo, Brazil. We have been working as software developers for at least 10 years each, and have good experience with Open Source software.
What do you do? In summary, we help companies interact with the Open Source world, providing guidance to create communities around products, understand the benefits and drawbacks when working with Open Source, and help companies financially sponsor development of projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is public and what is not?</title>
      <link>https://t0.network/about/what-is-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://t0.network/about/what-is-public/</guid>
      <description>Anything is considered &amp;ldquo;public&amp;rdquo; unless said otherwise. That includes, but it is not limited by:
 Organizational Structure Communication Channels Budgets and Transaction Lists (possibly anonymized). Data on management platforms, such as JIRA or Basecamp. Code.  In general, any form of private communication is done via private means (e-mails, direct messages), and anything with bigger reach is public.
&amp;ldquo;Public&amp;rdquo;, in those terms, means that the information can be found online on a website that does not require the creation of an account to view the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://t0.network/about/coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://t0.network/about/coc/</guid>
      <description>Tier0 and all its associates are expected to follow the Contributor Covenant v1.4.
In addition, some other behaviors are considered unacceptable:
 Discrimination based on political alignment, such as publicly ask for removal of members for subscribing to certain political stances. Public targeting of other members of the community without going through the normal process.  We don&amp;rsquo;t have yet an email for reporting incidents, so for now if any happen contact someone on the core team.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>